https://www.ackahlaw.com/privacy-policy

(403) 452-9515
Book a Consultation
Home
Corporate Immigration
Cross-Border Business Immigration: Canada and U.S.
Careers
Why Choose Ackah Law?
Why Hire An Immigration Lawyer?
Corporate Immigration
We exclusively practice immigration law and provide comprehensive expertise in all areas of Canadian and United States immigration law. Our innovative legal practice combines professional knowledge, personal attention, and supportive advice to help you meet your cross-border business goals.
Learn More
Why Choose Ackah Law?
Why Hire An Immigration Lawyer?
Cross-Border Business Immigration: Canada and U.S.
U.S. Business Visitor and Tourist Visas
Self-Employed
Treaty Traders and Investor E-1 and E-2 Visas
Specialty Occupations: H-1B Visa
Study Permit: F-1 Visa
Intra-Company Transfers: L-1 Visa
TN NAFTA Visa
Business Travel to Canada
Personal Immigration
People want to travel or move to Canada or the United States for many reasons - for work, for vacation, for study or to join their family. A mistake on your application, not sending an important document or forgetting to submit an application fee can cost you time and money - and can result in your immigration application being denied.
Learn More
Why Choose Ackah Law?
Why Hire An Immigration Lawyer?
How to Move to Canada
How to Move to Canada from the United States
IEC Young Professionals
IEC Working Holiday Program
Economic Immigration
Business Immigration
Temporary Work Permits
Study in Canada
Frances Hayden
See also:
About
Careers
Contact
FAQ
Referral Program
Testimonials
Why Choose Ackah Law?
Why Hire An Immigration Lawyer?
Resources
News
Book a Consultation
Search Ackah Law...
Contact us
Contact Information
1 (403) 452-9515
1 (800) 932-1190
Book a Consultation
More Options...
Privacy Policy
Information Security and Quality
Ackah Business Immigration Law (“Ackah Law”) is committed to protecting your personal information and to maintaining its confidentiality. We implement appropriate secure measures and processes when transmitting sensitive information to ensure your information is always protected.
By using www.ackahlaw.com (the “Website”) or by accepting the Terms of Use (via opt-in, checkbox, pop-up, or clicking an email link confirming the same), you agreed to be bound by our terms and this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect
When you visit our Website, we will collect certain information about you.
To provide you with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service and attention, and to accommodate certain requests which you make, we request information about you in certain circumstances and collect certain information automatically.
Consistent with our previous practices, we will only collect and process your personal data when we have a lawful basis for doing so. This lawful basis includes when you provide us with consent, when we have a contractual obligation to collect or process the data, and when we have a legitimate interest in managing your personal data.
We may collect and/or receive the following types of information from you:
Information Provided Voluntarily
Personal Information: You may be asked to provide personal information including your name, address, email address and phone number when you sign up for any of our newsletters, respond to a survey, register for a webinar, or purchase a service. We will only request the personal information that is required to fulfill our obligations to you, i.e. to deliver what you have requested, as well as to comply with any legal obligations that may accompany such an exchange.
Billing Information: If you obtain services from Ackah Law, we track certain information about the services you purchase. You will also be required to provide additional information required for processing your payment. This generally includes a credit card or other payment information, expiration dates, card security codes, your billing address or similar information. This information is generally processed and captured by third-party vendors, such as payment processors and merchant account providers. Third-party vendors who assist us in any of our business functions will also be doing so pursuant to their own terms and conditions, including privacy policies and terms of use.
Information Collected Automatically
In addition to the information described above, we may collect some or all of the following information:
Activity Info (Log Data): Information may be collected based on your use of the Website, which generally includes information about your computer hardware and software, such as:
Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, operating systems, browser types, device types, URLS, access dates and times; Website pages that you visit; referring website information; universally unique identifiers (“UUID”), advertising identifier (“IDFA”), carrier and country location, hardware and processor information, network type, and other related data.
Use of Cookies: Our website may use cookies to deliver a better experience for you. Cookies are files with small amounts of data that a website stores on your computer’s or mobile device’s hard drive so that certain information about your visit and web-browsing preferences will be recognized upon a return visit. Cookies serve functions such as “remembering” log-in names and passwords, or enabling or saving shopping cart contents. Like many websites, we may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to help us improve the experience you have with our Website. Most web browsers have a function that allows you to delete existing cookies on your device or you can set your browser options to that your device does not receive or accept cookies. Doing this may interfere with your ability to use the Website.
Third-Party Analytics: We use third-party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate and aggregate visitor data. These services help us evaluate Visitors’ use of the Website, including time spent on certain pages, which areas of the Website receive the most traffic, how often visitors visit pages within the Website, and provide general geographic location about visitors, the source of referred traffic (from other websites, vs search engines, etc.). These third party analytic services use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us with data. By providing your consent to this Privacy Policy, you consent to the collection and review of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out herein.
Other Third-Party Tracking Tools: We may also collect or receive information from third parties, such as Facebook, Instagram and/or other third-party social media and similar sites.
How to Access Your Personal Information
To manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications, you may unsubscribe by clicking the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any related email from Ackah Law. Emails related to the delivery of services are provided automatically – Customers are not always able to opt out of transactional emails. We will try to accommodate any requests related to the management of Personal Information in a timely manner. However, it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases (for example, if we have a legal obligation to keep it for certain timeframes, for example).
How We Use and Share the Information
We use the collected Information to understand customer needs, including regarding our Website services to:
present you with information through our Website and email services;provide our services, process orders, and administer our programs;maintain and improve our Website;respond to your requests, and provide customer service, including in response to any problems that may arise, such as difficulties in navigating our Website or accessing certain features;solicit your feedback, and to inform you about our services and those of our third-party marketing partners that we feel may be of interest or value to you;personalize or display advertisements to you on third-party platforms;improve our services or offerings; andfulfill our legal or contractual obligations to you.
As with transactions elsewhere, when you purchase services your credit card company will also retain certain information regarding your purchase. We will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company without your permission.
We may share the Information collected with joint venture partners, affiliates, agents, current or prospective business partners, businesses under common control, third-party businesses or partners participating in administering our services, or to those providing business functions such as technical support, customer service, marketing assistance, etc. These businesses will only have access to information as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law.
In the event of the sale or transfer of our business to a third-party buyer, including in the event of bankruptcy or liquidation, we may, as necessary, share your data with the buyer or transferee.
In the event that we have to collect on a debt owed to us by you, we may, as necessary, share your information with an attorney or a court of law to enforce our rights and collect what is owed.
Under certain circumstances we may be obligated or compelled to disclose the Information: when required by law, court order or government agency, or when disclosing such Information is reasonably required to protect Ackah Law, its property, the Website, the safety of visitors or others.
Retargeting/Personalized and Behavioral Ads
We may, using the techniques described above, and in conjunction with third party marketing partners, gather information from your visit to our Website for purposes of providing relevant advertising content to you in the future. This means that through third-party marketing partners or third-party sites such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, we may display advertisements to you (remarketing or retargeting), based on usage data collected during your visit to our website.
Google Ad Words: We may utilize Google Ad Words, which provides certain information collected on our website to the Adwords advertising network.
Security of Your Information
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our services providers, which we believe is sufficient for the information involved, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Because we work with third-party businesses and vendors in various aspects of our business including operating this website, database management, website security, etc., we cannot guarantee the absolute security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the Information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. Any information that you provide to us via email should be treated with extra caution, as we cannot control the level of security available through email providers.
Children
We are strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Website. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage all parents to talk to their children about online safety and to monitor their children’s use of the Internet. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will make best efforts to immediately delete that information from our databases.
Visitors Outside Canada
Our Website and the servers that make this Website available worldwide are located in Canada. The Internet laws in Canada govern all matters relating to this Website. Any information you provide in subscribing to or visiting our Website will be transferred to Canada. By visiting our Website and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing, and use.
EU Visitors and the GDPR
If you live in the EU, certain parts of your data may be subject to protection by the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”), a privacy regulation intended to help you have greater control over your personal data.
Under the GDPR, you have the right:
to know what information is being collected, as disclosed in this Privacy Policy (“right to transparent information”);to object on grounds relating to your particular situation to the collection or processing of certain kinds of information (“right to object”);to withdraw consent even after it has been given, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing of your data prior to your withdrawal (“right to withdraw consent”);to access, modify or update your information so that it is correct (“right to access” and “right to rectification”);to have your information deleted or erased (“right to erasure” or “right to be forgotten”);to have your data transferred or ported elsewhere (“right to data portability”);and the right to restrict processing in certain situations (“right to restriction of processing”).
For purposes of the GDPR, to the fullest extent possible we do not directly collect or maintain personal data of our EU visitors or clients. This is done through partnerships with third-party vendors who have systems designed for the collection and storage of data on behalf of their clients (“data processors”). The data is only kept as long as is reasonably required to accomplish the purpose or purposes for which it was collected. Certain data may be expunged or utilized more quickly than others, and depending on your engagement and behaviors, including purchasing behaviors, we may be engaged in a business or contractual relationship with some longevity. (For example, if you purchase services that span over some time, you will continue to receive communications in regard to those services).
The categories of data processors with whom we work, and that help us in the collection of information that allows us to serve and interact with you include website analytics provider(s), website and webform plug-ins and related third-party services that allow us to maintain an up-to-date online platform and communicate with you electronically, an email service provider or providers to assist in managing email correspondence with our visitors, customers and list, as well as payment processor(s) and/or merchant account(s) to help us transact sales online and follow up with you regarding any purchases.
You may contact us at any time to have your information with any of these processors updated or corrected, deleted, or to obtain a copy for your records. Additionally, you may opt out of receiving any additional emails or marketing messages from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our email notifications.
Further, if you feel that we have not complied with the relevant data protection regulations, please contact us by sending us an email at contact@ackahlaw.com with your first and last name, your country of origin, and a summary of your concern or complaint. We will endeavor to respond at our earliest possible convenience to address your concern. If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may have additional options.
Residents in Designated Countries may also have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant EU data protection authority. You may access a list of the Data Protection Authorities in the EU here.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Ackah Law may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. Please review the Privacy Policy when you visit our Website to remain updated on our current policy. We have no intentions of making any changes to our Privacy Policy and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past. By accessing the Website and/or using our services after making any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, our use of the Information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect the information. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Whenever we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will update the date at the top.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at contact@ackahlaw.com with “Privacy Policy” in the subject line.
*Please note that this immigration website has been created for informational purposes only and cannot be relied upon as legal advice. Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 Ackah Business Immigration Law.
